<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ZikiChombo</title>
    <link>http://zikichombo.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ZikiChombo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 19:26:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zikichombo.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Commercial and General Sponsorship</title>
      <link>http://zikichombo.org/contrib/sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 19:26:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zikichombo.org/contrib/sponsor/</guid>
      <description>Commercial contributions and General Sponsorship If you are putting ZikiChombo code to commercial use, we kindly request that you estimate a fair and reasonable value that it provides, commenserate with your sales, and figure out how to give back by examing the options here. This will help maintain our OSS quality standards and ultimately your benefit.
When you give money for ZikiChombo, the money is directed to IRI France, SAS, a French 1 person LLC dedicated to R&amp;amp;D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer Contributions</title>
      <link>http://zikichombo.org/contrib/dev/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 19:26:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zikichombo.org/contrib/dev/</guid>
      <description>Developer Contributions Developers provide support by engaging our project.
Giving our libraries a shot. Using and trying to use our libraries on a test run helps. Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t end up doing much, it gives you the opportunity to give us feedback and file issues.
Filing issues The filing of issues comprises major and irreplacable contributions. It lets us track and resolve problems.
Send us pull requests You can send pull requests, and we can incorporate them after review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launch!</title>
      <link>http://zikichombo.org/blog/launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zikichombo.org/blog/launch/</guid>
      <description>Launching zikichombo We have decided to launch ZikiChombo after careful consideration of our own private work and several interesting public go audio projects, discussions, and proposals.
Background. In 2015, Rakyll proposed. audio I/O in the scope of the go mobile project. This project has sparked a lot of interest amongst gophers, giving rise to the shiny interface for example. The scope of the proposal was in our opinion a bit too focused on Android and Go access to mobile apps, and decided to use openal as the backing component.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>